(Sheldon:)I can barely hear you
over my theremin.
(Sheldon:)Well, that was a
little uncalled for.
(Leonard:)No, that was
completely called for.
(Leonard:)We need quiet.
(Sheldon:)So, your project is more
important than mine?
(Leonard:)Well, seeing as your project
is to sabotage my project, yes.
(Sheldon:)Don't beat around the bush,
Leonard.
(Sheldon:)If you don't want me here,
(Sheldon:)just say the word,
and I'll leave.
(Sheldon:)Could have beaten
around the bush a little.
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ The trouble I've seen ♪
♪ Nobody knows my sorrow ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh. ♪
(Penny:)What you doing?
(Penny:)Trying to contact
your home planet?
(Sheldon:)I'm practicing my theremin.
(Leonard:)Oh.